

portfolio: www.elementten.com projects: www.github.com/neonwednesdays

Summary

A versatile and creative programmer and developer who also concerns himself with design and user experience. With multiple programming language backgrounds and familiarity in graphic design tools, he hopes to develop applications that promote creativity and interactivity in technology.

Education

August 2010 to December 2014 **Georgia Institute of Technology**

Graduated with Bachelors in Computational Media with a focus on Media and

Development

Skills

Development & Design Skillset

JavaCSSUnity3DJavascriptHTMLIllustratorJQueryAngularJSPhotoshopReact JSGitSemantic UI

Experience

March 2015 to Current **Promethean Inc.**

Worked as a Front End Developer, utilizing Javascript using React as a framework to implement various features for a web application for schools. Also used HTML and CSS to build component structures and designs for other developers based on mockups.

August 2014 to December 2014 MentorWeb

Implemented the front end interface using AngularJS and Semantic UI in conjunction with HTML and CSS for a web application based on client specifications for the purposes of matching mentees with mentors. Worked with a team using the Agile

June 2013 to July 2014 WorkReadyGrad

Created animations and videos using Flash and After Effects as an intern for a startup

focusing on college education plans.

January 2014 to April 2014 Game Studio at Georgia Tech

Collaborated and prototyped augmented reality games utilizing Qualcomm's Vuforia

and Unity programming in C# to build 3D games meant to be showcased.

Other

August 2014 to August 2015 Atlanta Humane Society

Volunteered and cared for animals to get them comfortable for adoption.

Personal

Participated in many hackathons and game jams to create applications and game

prototypes within a 48 hour deadline.